<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<mes:GenericMetadata xmlns:mes="http://www.sdmx.org/resources/sdmxml/schemas/v2_1/message" xmlns:gen="http://www.sdmx.org/resources/sdmxml/schemas/v2_1/metadata/generic" xmlns:com="http://www.sdmx.org/resources/sdmxml/schemas/v2_1/common">
  <mes:Header>
    <mes:ID>IREF1627150579</mes:ID>
    <mes:Test>True</mes:Test>
    <mes:Prepared>2021-07-24T18:16:19</mes:Prepared>
    <mes:Sender id="open-sdg_sdg-build@1-4-0"/>
    <mes:Structure structureID="MDS1">
      <com:Structure>
        <URN>urn:sdmx:org.sdmx.infomodel.metadatastructure.MetadataStructure=IAEG-SDGs:SDG_MSD(0.3)</URN>
      </com:Structure>
    </mes:Structure>
  </mes:Header>
  
  <mes:MetadataSet structureRef="MDS1" setID="297f28d9-be89-44d0-bee4-2fd623a37f1d">
    <com:Name xml:lang="en">SDG METADATA SET</com:Name>
    <gen:Report id="SDG_META_RPT">
      <gen:Target id="KEY_TARGET">
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="DIMENSION_DESCRIPTOR_VALUES_TARGET">
          <gen:DataKey>
            <com:KeyValue id="SERIES">
              <com:Value>SL_EMP_GTOTL</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REPORTING_TYPE">
              <com:Value>N</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REF_AREA">
              <com:Value>KG</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
          </gen:DataKey>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="Dataflow">
          <gen:ObjectReference>
            <URN>urn:sdmx:org.sdmx.infomodel.datastructure.Dataflow=IAEG-SDGs:DF_SDG_GLC(1.0)</URN>
          </gen:ObjectReference>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
      </gen:Target>
      <gen:AttributeSet>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_GOAL">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Goal 10. Reduce inequality within and among countries]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_TARGET">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[10.4 Adopt policies, especially fiscal, wage and social protection policies, and progressively achieve greater equality]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_INDICATOR">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[10.4.1. Labour share of GDP, comprising wages and social protection transfers]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="ORGANISATION_UNIT">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The National Statistical Committee of the Kyrgyz Republic (Office for Economic Statistics and National Accounts)]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_NAME">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[E. K. Isenkulova]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_EMAIL">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[eisenkulova@stat.kg]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_PHONE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[(0312) 32 46 95]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="STAT_CONC_DEF">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Labour share of Gross Domestic Product (GDP) is the total compensation of employees given as a percent of GDP, which is a measure of total output. It provides information about the relative share of output which is paid as compensation to employees as compared with the share paid to capital in the production process for a given reference period.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="RATIONALE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The method of GDP formation by sources of income is one of the three methods used by the National Statistical Committee of the Kyrgyz Republic to calculate GDP under SNA-1993 and 2008. However, it is not the main method, because according to the adopted methodology not all income indicators are obtained by direct account, some of them are calculated using the balance method.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SOURCE_TYPE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The National Statistical Committee performs data collection, processing and calculation.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COMPILING_ORG">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Показатель расчетный, при котором используются данные отраслевой статистики, Министерства финансов, Социального фонда и Национального банка Кыргызской Республики Периодичность: годовая.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="DATA_COMP">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The indicator on labour share of GDP, including compensations and salaries and social security payments is calculated as follows: 
LF share = Wage/GDP*100,
where
LF share is Labour force share,
Wage - Total compensation of employees,
GDP - Gross Domestic Product (GDP).]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="REC_USE_LIM">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[In general, labour share in GDP will underestimate the proportion of GDP accrued to total employment, as it covers only the compensation of employees and does not include the labour income of the selfemployed. 
Thus the indicator may be less relevant in countries where a large proportion of employment is in self-employment. However, an adjusted labour share may be estimated to take into account the labour income of self-employed workers.
GDP may exclude or underreport activities that are difficult to measure, such as transactions in the informal sector or in illegal markets, etc. thus understating the GDP. Moreover, GDP does not account for the social and environmental costs of production, and is therefore is not a good measure of the level of over-all wellbeing.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="QUALITY_ASSURE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Logical and arithmetic control of the reporting data is conducted.ik5r6]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COVERAGE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Dynamic data since 1993 are available at the website of the National Statistical Committee.www.stat.kg]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COMPARABILITY">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The Kyrgyz Republic payroll data are available to be compared upon request from international organizations (questionnaires are completed).]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="OTHER_DOC">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The Kyrgyz Republic SDG National Reporting Platform: https://sustainabledevelopment-kyrgyzstan.github.io/16-7-1/ 
The UN System of National Accounts – UN SNA-1993 and SNA 2008:
Recommendations of the CIS-STAT Committee on the Generation of Income Account. Moscow, 1995: European System of Integrated Economic Accounts 1995.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
      </gen:AttributeSet>
    </gen:Report>
  </mes:MetadataSet>
  
  <mes:MetadataSet structureRef="MDS1" setID="5e141956-f465-45b7-8e99-5a1fe4aa6211">
    <com:Name xml:lang="en">SDG METADATA SET</com:Name>
    <gen:Report id="SDG_META_RPT">
      <gen:Target id="KEY_TARGET">
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="DIMENSION_DESCRIPTOR_VALUES_TARGET">
          <gen:DataKey>
            <com:KeyValue id="SERIES">
              <com:Value>SI_POV_50MI</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REPORTING_TYPE">
              <com:Value>N</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REF_AREA">
              <com:Value>KG</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
          </gen:DataKey>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="Dataflow">
          <gen:ObjectReference>
            <URN>urn:sdmx:org.sdmx.infomodel.datastructure.Dataflow=IAEG-SDGs:DF_SDG_GLC(1.0)</URN>
          </gen:ObjectReference>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
      </gen:Target>
      <gen:AttributeSet>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_GOAL">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Goal 10. Reduce inequality within and among countries]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_TARGET">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[10.2. By 2030, empower and promote the social, economic and political inclusion of all, irrespective of age, sex, disability, race, ethnicity, origin, religion or economic or other status]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_INDICATOR">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[10.2.1. Proportion of people living below 50 per cent of median income, by sex, age and persons with disabilities]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="ORGANISATION_UNIT">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[National Statistics Committee of the Kyrgyz Republic (Household Statistics Division)
The National Statistical Committee of the Kyrgyz Republic (Household Statistics Division)]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_NAME">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Y. I. Kalymbetova]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_EMAIL">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Y.Kalymbetova@stat.kg ]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_PHONE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[(312) 66 41 64]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="STAT_CONC_DEF">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The proportion of people living below 50 percent of median income (or consumption) is the share (%) of a country’s population living on less than half of the consumption/income level of the median of the national income/consumption distribution. ]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="RATIONALE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[This indicator is an indicator of relative poverty and inequality of the income distribution within a country. This indicator and similar relative measures are commonly used for poverty measurement in rich countries and are increasingly also used as a complementary measure of inequality and poverty in low- and middleincome countries. ]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SOURCE_TYPE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[National household surveys on population income and expenditure.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COMPILING_ORG">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Интегрированное обследование бюджетов домашних хозяйств и рабочей силы проводится ежеквартально во всех регионах страны. Программа обследования содержит специальный модуль "Доходы и расходы домашнего хозяйства".]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="DATA_COMP">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Average per capita monetary income is ranked in ascending order. The indicator is calculated by estimating the share (in percent) of the population living on less than 50% of median of the national distribution of income or consumption.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="REC_USE_LIM">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[This indicator describes relative poverty and is based on the welfare indicator 40of a particular country.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="QUALITY_ASSURE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ Data quality is ensured through random household budget and labour force surveys in line with international recommendations]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COMPARABILITY">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Data are internationally comparable, as random household budget and labour force surveys are conducted in line with international recommendations]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="OTHER_DOC">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The Kyrgyz Republic SDG National Reporting Platform: https://sustainabledevelopment-kyrgyzstan.github.io]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
      </gen:AttributeSet>
    </gen:Report>
  </mes:MetadataSet>
  
  <mes:MetadataSet structureRef="MDS1" setID="0b2b74ee-1c1d-4cda-b200-3410fe0d3ca9">
    <com:Name xml:lang="en">SDG METADATA SET</com:Name>
    <gen:Report id="SDG_META_RPT">
      <gen:Target id="KEY_TARGET">
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="DIMENSION_DESCRIPTOR_VALUES_TARGET">
          <gen:DataKey>
            <com:KeyValue id="SERIES">
              <com:Value>SI_HEI_TOTL</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REPORTING_TYPE">
              <com:Value>N</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REF_AREA">
              <com:Value>KG</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
          </gen:DataKey>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="Dataflow">
          <gen:ObjectReference>
            <URN>urn:sdmx:org.sdmx.infomodel.datastructure.Dataflow=IAEG-SDGs:DF_SDG_GLC(1.0)</URN>
          </gen:ObjectReference>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
      </gen:Target>
      <gen:AttributeSet>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_GOAL">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Goal 10. Reduce inequality within and among countries]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_TARGET">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[10.1. By 2030, progressively achieve and sustain the above national average income growth among the poorest 40 per cent of the population]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_INDICATOR">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[10.1.1. Growth rate of household expenditure or per capita income among the poorest 40 per cent of the population and the population in general]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="ORGANISATION_UNIT">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The National Statistical Committee of the Kyrgyz Republic (Household Statistics Division)]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_NAME">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Y. I. Kalymbetova]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_EMAIL">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Y.Kalymbetova@stat.kg ]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_PHONE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[(312) 66 41 64]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="STAT_CONC_DEF">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The growth rate in the welfare aggregate of bottom 40% is computed as the annualized average growth rate in per capita real consumption or income of the bottom 40% of the income distribution in a country from household surveys over a roughly 5-year period. The national average growth rate in the welfare
aggregate is computed as the annualized average growth rate in per capita real consumption or income of the total population in a country from household surveys over a roughly 5-year period.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="RATIONALE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Improvements in shared prosperity require both a growing economy and a consideration of equity. Shared prosperity explicitly recognizes that while growth is necessary for improving economic welfare in a society, progress is measured by how those gains are shared with its poorest members. Moreover, in an inclusive society it is not sufficient to raise everyone above an absolute inimum standard of living; it must ensure that economic growth increases prosperity among the poor over time.
The decision to measure shared prosperity based on income or consumption was not taken to ignore the many other dimensions of welfare. It is motivated by the need for an indicator that is easy to understand, communicate, and measure—though measurement challenges exist. Indeed, shared prosperity comprises many dimensions of well-being of the less well-off, and when analyzing shared prosperity in the context of a country, it is important to consider a wide range of indicators of welfare.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SOURCE_TYPE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[National representative household surveys, including income or consumption module.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COMPILING_ORG">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Репрезентативные национальные обследования домашних хозяйств ]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="DATA_COMP">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Growth rates are calculated as annualized average growth rates over a roughly five-year period. ]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="REC_USE_LIM">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[There are mainly two limitations of shared prosperity indicators: data availability and data quality.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COMPARABILITY">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[To generate measures of shared prosperity that are reasonably comparable across countries, the World Bank Group has a standardized approach for choosing time periods, data sources, and other relevant parameters.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="OTHER_DOC">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[SDG National Reporting Platform: https://sustainabledevelopment-kyrgyzstan.github.io 
Data are published in statistical compendiums “Employment and Unemployment”, “Women and Men in the Kyrgyz Republic”, “Kyrgyzstan in Figures”]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
      </gen:AttributeSet>
    </gen:Report>
  </mes:MetadataSet>
  
  <mes:MetadataSet structureRef="MDS1" setID="1b4dcc4e-a17a-4d80-9c7b-6e97eeabe8c8">
    <com:Name xml:lang="en">SDG METADATA SET</com:Name>
    <gen:Report id="SDG_META_RPT">
      <gen:Target id="KEY_TARGET">
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="DIMENSION_DESCRIPTOR_VALUES_TARGET">
          <gen:DataKey>
            <com:KeyValue id="SERIES">
              <com:Value>VC_VOV_DCMN</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REPORTING_TYPE">
              <com:Value>N</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REF_AREA">
              <com:Value>KG</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
          </gen:DataKey>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="Dataflow">
          <gen:ObjectReference>
            <URN>urn:sdmx:org.sdmx.infomodel.datastructure.Dataflow=IAEG-SDGs:DF_SDG_GLC(1.0)</URN>
          </gen:ObjectReference>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
      </gen:Target>
      <gen:AttributeSet>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_GOAL">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Goal 10. Reduce inequality within and among countries]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_TARGET">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[10.3. Ensure equal opportunity and reduce inequalities of outcome, including by eliminating discriminatory laws, policies and practices and promoting appropriate legislation, policies and action in this regard ]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_INDICATOR">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[10.3.1. Proportion of population reporting having personally felt discriminated against or harassed in the previous 12 months on the basis of a ground of discrimination prohibited under international human rights law]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="ORGANISATION_UNIT">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The National Statistical Committee of the Kyrgyz Republic (Household Statistics Division)]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_NAME">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Y. I. Kalymbetova]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_EMAIL">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Y.Kalymbetova@stat.kg ]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_PHONE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[(312) 66 41 64]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="STAT_CONC_DEF">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Discrimination means negative or biased treatment of a person, or deprivation of certain rights on any ground.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="RATIONALE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Discrimination can impede individuals from getting a fair and equal access to opportunities and services. These questions are designed to assess cases of discrimination and harassment against respondents that occurred during the 12 months prior to the survey. The questions include specific causes of discrimination and harassment, which may help respondents to remember the events. The current questions are based on the recommended set of questions at the beginning of the sixth round of the Multiple Indicator Cluster Survey.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SOURCE_TYPE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Demographic and Health Surveys (DHS), Multiple Indicator Cluster Survey (MICS).]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COMPILING_ORG">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Этот показатель рассчитывается на основе данных кластерного обследования по многим показателям (MICS). Данные собраны для целевой группы - женщины в возрасте 15-49 лет.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="DATA_COMP">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[This indicator means the proportion of persons who responded positively to the number of persons in the target group. The indicator value of the allegedly discriminated group is divided by the indicator value of another group. At the same time, the indicator calculates the proportion of women aged 15-49 years who have experienced at least one type of discrimination by the total discrimination cases based on each of the seven grounds over the last 12 months.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="REC_USE_LIM">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The questions are based on the recommended set of questions available in the sixth round of the Multiple Indicator Cluster Survey. The questions may change based on the methodology developments to move the indicator from SDG Level III to SDG Level II.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COVERAGE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[2018 Multiple Indicator Cluster Survey in the Kyrgyz Republic]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="OTHER_DOC">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The Kyrgyz Republic SDG National Reporting Platform: https://sustainabledevelopment-kyrgyzstan.github.io
 https://www.unicef.org]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
      </gen:AttributeSet>
    </gen:Report>
  </mes:MetadataSet>
  
  <mes:MetadataSet structureRef="MDS1" setID="aad8eba6-df2f-4088-a21b-ba7b49ae5391">
    <com:Name xml:lang="en">SDG METADATA SET</com:Name>
    <gen:Report id="SDG_META_RPT">
      <gen:Target id="KEY_TARGET">
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="DIMENSION_DESCRIPTOR_VALUES_TARGET">
          <gen:DataKey>
            <com:KeyValue id="SERIES">
              <com:Value>VC_VOV_GDSD</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REPORTING_TYPE">
              <com:Value>N</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REF_AREA">
              <com:Value>KG</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
          </gen:DataKey>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="Dataflow">
          <gen:ObjectReference>
            <URN>urn:sdmx:org.sdmx.infomodel.datastructure.Dataflow=IAEG-SDGs:DF_SDG_GLC(1.0)</URN>
          </gen:ObjectReference>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
      </gen:Target>
      <gen:AttributeSet>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_GOAL">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Goal 10. Reduce inequality within and among countries]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_TARGET">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[10.3. Ensure equal opportunity and reduce inequalities of outcome, including by eliminating discriminatory laws, policies and practices and promoting appropriate legislation, policies and action in this regard ]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_INDICATOR">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[10.3.1. Proportion of population reporting having personally felt discriminated against or harassed in the previous 12 months on the basis of a ground of discrimination prohibited under international human rights law]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="ORGANISATION_UNIT">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The National Statistical Committee of the Kyrgyz Republic (Household Statistics Division)]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_NAME">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Y. I. Kalymbetova]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_EMAIL">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Y.Kalymbetova@stat.kg ]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_PHONE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[(312) 66 41 64]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="STAT_CONC_DEF">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Discrimination means negative or biased treatment of a person, or deprivation of certain rights on any ground.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="RATIONALE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Discrimination can impede individuals from getting a fair and equal access to opportunities and services. These questions are designed to assess cases of discrimination and harassment against respondents that occurred during the 12 months prior to the survey. The questions include specific causes of discrimination and harassment, which may help respondents to remember the events. The current questions are based on the recommended set of questions at the beginning of the sixth round of the Multiple Indicator Cluster Survey.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SOURCE_TYPE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Demographic and Health Surveys (DHS), Multiple Indicator Cluster Survey (MICS).]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COMPILING_ORG">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Этот показатель рассчитывается на основе данных кластерного обследования по многим показателям (MICS). Данные собраны для целевой группы - женщины в возрасте 15-49 лет.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="DATA_COMP">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[This indicator means the proportion of persons who responded positively to the number of persons in the target group. The indicator value of the allegedly discriminated group is divided by the indicator value of another group. At the same time, the indicator calculates the proportion of women aged 15-49 years who have experienced at least one type of discrimination by the total discrimination cases based on each of the seven grounds over the last 12 months.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="REC_USE_LIM">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The questions are based on the recommended set of questions available in the sixth round of the Multiple Indicator Cluster Survey. The questions may change based on the methodology developments to move the indicator from SDG Level III to SDG Level II.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COVERAGE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[2018 Multiple Indicator Cluster Survey in the Kyrgyz Republic]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="OTHER_DOC">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The Kyrgyz Republic SDG National Reporting Platform: https://sustainabledevelopment-kyrgyzstan.github.io
 https://www.unicef.org]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
      </gen:AttributeSet>
    </gen:Report>
  </mes:MetadataSet>
  
</mes:GenericMetadata>
        