<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<mes:GenericMetadata xmlns:mes="http://www.sdmx.org/resources/sdmxml/schemas/v2_1/message" xmlns:gen="http://www.sdmx.org/resources/sdmxml/schemas/v2_1/metadata/generic" xmlns:com="http://www.sdmx.org/resources/sdmxml/schemas/v2_1/common">
  <mes:Header>
    <mes:ID>IREF1627150557</mes:ID>
    <mes:Test>True</mes:Test>
    <mes:Prepared>2021-07-24T18:15:57</mes:Prepared>
    <mes:Sender id="open-sdg_sdg-build@1-4-0"/>
    <mes:Structure structureID="MDS1">
      <com:Structure>
        <URN>urn:sdmx:org.sdmx.infomodel.metadatastructure.MetadataStructure=IAEG-SDGs:SDG_MSD(0.3)</URN>
      </com:Structure>
    </mes:Structure>
  </mes:Header>
  
  <mes:MetadataSet structureRef="MDS1" setID="a051bbdf-f701-46e8-941f-0bbd340cac1c">
    <com:Name xml:lang="en">SDG METADATA SET</com:Name>
    <gen:Report id="SDG_META_RPT">
      <gen:Target id="KEY_TARGET">
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="DIMENSION_DESCRIPTOR_VALUES_TARGET">
          <gen:DataKey>
            <com:KeyValue id="SERIES">
              <com:Value>SI_POV_NMPI</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REPORTING_TYPE">
              <com:Value>N</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REF_AREA">
              <com:Value>KG</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
          </gen:DataKey>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="Dataflow">
          <gen:ObjectReference>
            <URN>urn:sdmx:org.sdmx.infomodel.datastructure.Dataflow=IAEG-SDGs:DF_SDG_GLC(1.0)</URN>
          </gen:ObjectReference>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
      </gen:Target>
      <gen:AttributeSet>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_GOAL">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[1. End poverty in all its forms everywhere]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_TARGET">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[1.2: By 2030, reduce at least by half the proportion of men, women and children of all ages living in poverty in all its dimensions according to national definitions]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_INDICATOR">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[1.2.2: Proportion of men, women and children of all ages living in poverty in all its dimensions according to national definitions]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="ORGANISATION_UNIT">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[ National Statistical Committee of the Kyrgyz Republic (Household Statistics Division)]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_NAME">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Kerimalieva N.K.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_EMAIL">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Sdg_nsc@stat.kg ]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_PHONE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[(0312) 32 46 91]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="STAT_CONC_DEF">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Proportion of men, women and children of all ages living in poverty in all its dimensions (multidimensional poverty) is when an individual is unable to meet his basic needs in accordance with social norms and generally accepted standards.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="RATIONALE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Dimensions and indicators were selected in accordance with several guiding principles: well established multidimensional welfare indices, applicability to the Kyrgyz Republic context, relevance in the context of the Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs) and data availability.
There are theoretical and practical justifications for each dimension, emphasizing their importance as major welfare determinants. The NSDS of the Kyrgyz Republic sets targets for achieving by 2040 for each aspect of multidimensional poverty.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SOURCE_TYPE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Integrated Household Budget and Labour Force Sample Survey (hereinafter IHBLFSS).]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COMPILING_ORG">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Сбор данных осуществляется посредством вопросников ИОДХ с применением кластерной выборки, построенной на последней доступной Переписи населения и актуализированных списках жилых помещений. В опросах ИОДХ используется персональное интервью с использованием планшетных компьютеров (ComputerAssisted Personal Interview, CAPI).
Сбор данных осуществляется на ежеквартальной основе, разработка индикатора производится по итогам года. 
]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="DATA_COMP">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The National Multidimensional Poverty Index (NMPI) has been developed by the National Statistical Committee of the Kyrgyz Republic in cooperation with the United Nations Children’s Fund and the United Nations Development Programme. NMIP is calculated using the internationally recognized methodology of Sabina Alkire and James Foster. It is characterized by three main multidimensional poverty indicators. These are multidimensional poverty incidence (H), the average intensity of deprivation among the poor (A) and the National Multidimensional Poverty Index (M). 
Under these poor are considered those deprived of at least one third of the weighted indicators.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="REC_USE_LIM">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The National Multidimensional Poverty Index and its components allow assessing changes in the population’s quality of life over time and dynamics for different groups. When implemented at the inter-country level, such studies make it possible to compare States policies outcomes and, at the national level, meet the needs of comparative analysis of situation in country’s regions.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="QUALITY_ASSURE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The raw data are checked for quality before being submitted for further analysis.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COVERAGE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Data has been available since 2016.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COMPARABILITY">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Standard methodology is used, and the set of indicators included in the measurements is relevant for the Kyrgyz Republic]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="OTHER_DOC">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[KR National SDG Reporting Platform:  https://sustainabledevelopment-kyrgyzstan.github.io ]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
      </gen:AttributeSet>
    </gen:Report>
  </mes:MetadataSet>
  
</mes:GenericMetadata>
        