<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<mes:GenericMetadata xmlns:mes="http://www.sdmx.org/resources/sdmxml/schemas/v2_1/message" xmlns:gen="http://www.sdmx.org/resources/sdmxml/schemas/v2_1/metadata/generic" xmlns:com="http://www.sdmx.org/resources/sdmxml/schemas/v2_1/common">
  <mes:Header>
    <mes:ID>IREF1626258719</mes:ID>
    <mes:Test>True</mes:Test>
    <mes:Prepared>2021-07-14T10:31:59</mes:Prepared>
    <mes:Sender id="open-sdg_sdg-build@1-3-0"/>
    <mes:Structure structureID="MDS1">
      <com:Structure>
        <URN>urn:sdmx:org.sdmx.infomodel.metadatastructure.MetadataStructure=IAEG-SDGs:SDG_MSD(0.3)</URN>
      </com:Structure>
    </mes:Structure>
  </mes:Header>
  
  <mes:MetadataSet structureRef="MDS1" setID="b81d668e-e733-4044-b164-825faec1b20a">
    <com:Name xml:lang="en">SDG METADATA SET</com:Name>
    <gen:Report id="SDG_META_RPT">
      <gen:Target id="KEY_TARGET">
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="DIMENSION_DESCRIPTOR_VALUES_TARGET">
          <gen:DataKey>
            <com:KeyValue id="SERIES">
              <com:Value>SI_HEI_TOTL</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REPORTING_TYPE">
              <com:Value>N</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REF_AREA">
              <com:Value>KG</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
          </gen:DataKey>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="Dataflow">
          <gen:ObjectReference>
            <URN>urn:sdmx:org.sdmx.infomodel.datastructure.Dataflow=IAEG-SDGs:DF_SDG_GLC(1.0)</URN>
          </gen:ObjectReference>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
      </gen:Target>
      <gen:AttributeSet>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_GOAL">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Goal 10. Reduce inequality within and among countries]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_TARGET">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[10.1. By 2030, progressively achieve and sustain the above national average income growth among the poorest 40 per cent of the population]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_INDICATOR">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[10.1.1. Growth rate of household expenditure or per capita income among the poorest 40 per cent of the population and the population in general]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="ORGANISATION_UNIT">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The National Statistical Committee of the Kyrgyz Republic (Household Statistics Division)]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_NAME">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Y. I. Kalymbetova]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_EMAIL">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Y.Kalymbetova@stat.kg ]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_PHONE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[(312) 66 41 64]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="STAT_CONC_DEF">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[The growth rate in the welfare aggregate of bottom 40% is computed as the annualized average growth rate in per capita real consumption or income of the bottom 40% of the income distribution in a country from household surveys over a roughly 5-year period. The national average growth rate in the welfare
aggregate is computed as the annualized average growth rate in per capita real consumption or income of the total population in a country from household surveys over a roughly 5-year period.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="RATIONALE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Improvements in shared prosperity require both a growing economy and a consideration of equity. Shared prosperity explicitly recognizes that while growth is necessary for improving economic welfare in a society, progress is measured by how those gains are shared with its poorest members. Moreover, in an inclusive society it is not sufficient to raise everyone above an absolute inimum standard of living; it must ensure that economic growth increases prosperity among the poor over time.
The decision to measure shared prosperity based on income or consumption was not taken to ignore the many other dimensions of welfare. It is motivated by the need for an indicator that is easy to understand, communicate, and measure—though measurement challenges exist. Indeed, shared prosperity comprises many dimensions of well-being of the less well-off, and when analyzing shared prosperity in the context of a country, it is important to consider a wide range of indicators of welfare.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SOURCE_TYPE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[National representative household surveys, including income or consumption module.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COMPILING_ORG">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Репрезентативные национальные обследования домашних хозяйств ]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="DATA_COMP">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[Growth rates are calculated as annualized average growth rates over a roughly five-year period. ]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="REC_USE_LIM">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[There are mainly two limitations of shared prosperity indicators: data availability and data quality.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COMPARABILITY">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[To generate measures of shared prosperity that are reasonably comparable across countries, the World Bank Group has a standardized approach for choosing time periods, data sources, and other relevant parameters.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="OTHER_DOC">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[SDG National Reporting Platform: https://sustainabledevelopment-kyrgyzstan.github.io 
Data are published in statistical compendiums “Employment and Unemployment”, “Women and Men in the Kyrgyz Republic”, “Kyrgyzstan in Figures”]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
      </gen:AttributeSet>
    </gen:Report>
  </mes:MetadataSet>
  
</mes:GenericMetadata>
        