<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<mes:GenericMetadata xmlns:mes="http://www.sdmx.org/resources/sdmxml/schemas/v2_1/message" xmlns:gen="http://www.sdmx.org/resources/sdmxml/schemas/v2_1/metadata/generic" xmlns:com="http://www.sdmx.org/resources/sdmxml/schemas/v2_1/common">
  <mes:Header>
    <mes:ID>IREF1627150557</mes:ID>
    <mes:Test>True</mes:Test>
    <mes:Prepared>2021-07-24T18:15:57</mes:Prepared>
    <mes:Sender id="open-sdg_sdg-build@1-4-0"/>
    <mes:Structure structureID="MDS1">
      <com:Structure>
        <URN>urn:sdmx:org.sdmx.infomodel.metadatastructure.MetadataStructure=IAEG-SDGs:SDG_MSD(0.3)</URN>
      </com:Structure>
    </mes:Structure>
  </mes:Header>
  
  <mes:MetadataSet structureRef="MDS1" setID="fea62fff-4429-4f3a-9df5-4c564390b13c">
    <com:Name xml:lang="en">SDG METADATA SET</com:Name>
    <gen:Report id="SDG_META_RPT">
      <gen:Target id="KEY_TARGET">
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="DIMENSION_DESCRIPTOR_VALUES_TARGET">
          <gen:DataKey>
            <com:KeyValue id="SERIES">
              <com:Value>SE_TOT_PRFL</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REPORTING_TYPE">
              <com:Value>N</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
            <com:KeyValue id="REF_AREA">
              <com:Value>KG</com:Value>
            </com:KeyValue>
          </gen:DataKey>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
        <gen:ReferenceValue id="Dataflow">
          <gen:ObjectReference>
            <URN>urn:sdmx:org.sdmx.infomodel.datastructure.Dataflow=IAEG-SDGs:DF_SDG_GLC(1.0)</URN>
          </gen:ObjectReference>
        </gen:ReferenceValue>
      </gen:Target>
      <gen:AttributeSet>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_GOAL">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[4. Ensure inclusive and equitable quality education and promote lifelong learning opportunities for all]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_TARGET">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[4.1. By 2030, ensure that all girls and boys complete free, equitable and quality primary and secondary education leading to relevant and effective learning outcomes]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SDG_INDICATOR">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[4.1.1 Proportion of children and young people: 
(a) in grades 2/3; 
(b) at the end of primary; and 
(c) at the end of lower secondary achieving at least a minimum proficiency level in (i) reading and 
(ii) mathematics, by sex)]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="ORGANISATION_UNIT">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[1)National Statistical Committee of the Kyrgyz Republic (Sustainable Development and Environment Statistics Department)
2) Ministry of Education and Science of the Kyrgyz Republic
(National Center for Educational and Information Technology Quality Evaluation)]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_NAME">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[1) Kerimalieva Nazira Kerimalievna 
2) Shamshidinova Baktygul Sabyrzhanovna]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_EMAIL">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[1) Sdg_nsc@stat.kg 
2) bakula68@mail.ru]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="CONTACT_PHONE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[1) +996312 32 46 91
2) +996312622962]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="STAT_CONC_DEF">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[1) Percentage of children and young people at the end of primary education and the end of lower secondary education achieving at least a minimum proficiency level in (a) reading and (b) mathematics.
2) Percentage of children and young people in Grade 2 or 3 of primary education, at the end of primary education and the end of lower secondary education achieving at least a minimum proficiency level in (a) reading and (b) mathematics. The minimum proficiency level will be measured relative to new common reading and mathematics scales currently in development. 
As of August 2018 there is no globally accepted definition of the minimum proficiency level. As an interim reporting strategy, data reported according to the minimum proficiency level for each assessment]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="RATIONALE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[1) The indicator is a direct measure of the learning outcomes achieved in the two subject areas at the end of the relevant stages of education. The three measurement points will have their own established minimum standard. There is only one threshold that divides students into above and below minimum:
(a) Below minimum is the proportion or percentage of students who do not achieve a minimum standard as set up by countries according to the globally-defined minimum competencies.
(b) Above minimum is the proportion or percentage of students who have achieved the minimum standards. Due to heterogeneity of performance levels set by national and cross-national assessments, these performance levels will have to be mapped to the globally-defined minimum performance levels. Once the performance levels are mapped, the global education community will be able to identify for each country the proportion or percentage of children who achieved minimum standards. 

NASEA study was conducted based on stratified sample across the Kyrgyz Republic. The following strata were selected: categories of schools (Bishkek, regional centers and small towns, rural schools), languages of instruction (Kyrgyz, Russian, Uzbek) administrative regions of Kyrgyzstan.
Tests and questionnaires for students, school administrators and teachers are the NASEA tools. NASEA assessment matches results to students’ achievement levels.
The study uses four levels of educational achievement: below the basic (level 1), basic (level 2), above the basic (level 3), and high achievement (level 4). The minimum acceptable level is basic (2). The levels of students’ achievements were identified both in general terms and for each subject area, describing students results at a given level in accordance with national standards and programmes.
Grades 4 and 8 have been chosen for the study for the following reasons:
• Grade 4 completes primary school and serves as the basis for further education. Knowledge and skills acquired by students during primary school can be evaluated upon completion of this stage. It is particularly important to know what students have actually learned at the end of primary school, as further successful learning depends on it.
• Grade 8 for assessment was chosen by the Ministry of Education and Science. This grade precedes the final year of compulsory education, and assessment at this stage makes it possible to make the necessary adjustments in grade 9.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="SOURCE_TYPE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[1) Multiple Indicator Cluster Survey, 2018 (MICS)

2) Ministry of Education and Science of the Kyrgyz Republic. The National Assessment of Student Educational Achievements (NASEA). Study Report. Bishkek (2008, 2010, 2014, 2018)]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COMPILING_ORG">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[1) В опросах КОМП используется персональное интервью с использованием компьютеров (ComputerAssisted Personal Interview, CAPI). Приложение для сбора данных, в том числе специальная платформа управления данными КОМП, основано на программном обеспечении CSPro (Census and Survey Processing System) версии 6.3. Процедуры и стандартные программы, разработанные в рамках глобальной программы КОМП, были адаптированы к окончательной версии вопросника КОМП Кыргызстан, 2018 года и использовались в опросе.

2) Стратифицированная выборка на всей территории Кыргызской Республики. Страты по категориям школ: г. Бишкек, областные центры и малые города, школы сельской местности. Языки обучения: кыргызский, русский и узбекский.   Результаты теста и анкет (учащихся, администрации школ и учителей).]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="DATA_COMP">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[1) The indicator is calculated as the percentage of children and/or young people at the relevant stage of education achieving or exceeding a pre-defined proficiency level in a given subject.
Percentage of children between 7-14 years of age who successfully completed three basic reading and mathematics assignments.
2) 1,000 points on a scale describing students’ achievements at each level.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="REC_USE_LIM">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[1) While data from many national assessments are available now, every country sets its own standards so the performance levels might not be comparable.
2) NASEA measures students’ achievements against achievement levels rather than school grades.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COVERAGE">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[1) Data available on the NSC website
2) NASEA data available at:  http://testing.kg]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="COMPARABILITY">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[1) Currently every country sets its own standards so the performance levels might not be comparable.
2) NASEA results are not comparable with other international data because the tool was developed based on national educational standards and programmes of the Kyrgyz Republic.]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
        <gen:ReportedAttribute id="OTHER_DOC">
          
          <com:Text xml:lang="en"><![CDATA[KR National SDG Reporting Platform:
https://sustainabledevelopment-kyrgyzstan.github.io
Metadata of global and thematic indicators for SDG4 monitoring and review and «Education 2030»programme.
United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization. UNESCO Institute for statistics 2018.
The National Assessment of Student Educational Achievements (NASEA). Study Report. Bishkek (2008, 2010, 2014, 2018)Website: http://testing.kg]]></com:Text>
          
        </gen:ReportedAttribute>
        
      </gen:AttributeSet>
    </gen:Report>
  </mes:MetadataSet>
  
</mes:GenericMetadata>
        